Alejandro Valverde Mahou

Profile

Hard-working Student that loves machine learning, artificial intelligence and software development. Background in Computer Science and Engineering, pursuing a master to continue his studies specializing in Computer Vision, Deep Learning, Optimization Algorithms and Generative Models. Loves working in artificial intelligence, data science and software development related projects.

Publications

Learning to Generate 3D Representations of Building Roofs Using Single-View Aerial Imagery

Maxim Khomiakov, **Alejandro Valverde Mahou**, Alba Reinders Sánchez, Jes Frellsen , Michael Riis Andersen

ICASSP 2023

Education

MSc Eng in Human-Centered Artificial Intelligence, Technical University of Denmark, Copenhagen

September 2021 - February 2024

Focus on Artificial Intelligence, Deep Learning and Computer Vision, with multiple courses in Optimization and Algorithms. Special focus on Generative Models and Algorithms.

Bachelor in Computer Science and Engineering, Universidad Carlos III de Madrid, Madrid

September 2017 - July 2021

Took the Computer Science Minor with focus on Artificial Intelligence, Software Development, and Web Development. Bachelor thesis in Generative Adversarial Networks, awarded with a 10/10 with Honors.

Experience

Cofounder and tech member, rapidcreative.io, Copenhagen

February 2023 - Present

As a cofounder and full-stack developer at the startup rapidcreative.io, I develop web applications and user interfaces using Next.js and Python. Our company was established through the X-Tech program at DTU.

Student Assistant in the Engineering Team, ConWX, Copenhagen

May 2022 - Present

As a student assistant in ConWX's engineering team, I am developing a weather prediction web application using React. In this role, I collaborate with the team to create a seamless user experience and ensure the application meets the company's needs.

Internship in FrontEnd developer, Global Incubator, Madrid

June 2020 - September 2020

As a Frontend Developer intern, I utilized React to develop and improve web applications and user interfaces, working collaboratively with the development team to ensure optimal functionality and usability..

Hobbies

Reading, playing hockey and sports in general, learning Norse history and mythology, learning algorithms and techniques for applying them to my own projects as well as discovering new things in general, travelling and getting to know new cities, and cooking.



Details

avalverdemahou@gmail.com +34 654 51 67 26

Links

<u>LinkedIn</u>

GitHub

Personal WebPage

Languages

Spanish

••••

English

Cambridge English: Advanced (CAE) 2020

Competences

Deep Learning

Computer Vision

Data Science

Optimization Algorithms with Heuristics and Metaheuristics

Software Development

301tware Development

Complex Problem Solving Frontend Development

MLOps

Programming Languages

Python HTML, CSS & JavaScript

Julia C, C# , C++

Frameworks

PyTorch, TensorFlow & Scipy

Data Analysis and Visualization Libraries (NumPy, Matplotlib, Plotly, Dash, Pandas, Bokeh)

Next.js, React, Angular

Google Firebase

Unity, Godot

Git & GitHub

Overleaf & LaTeX

Jupyter Notebook & Google Colab

Blender